Tiller mss., 1963-1970 LMC 2528
Lilly Library
Tiller mss.
1963-1970
Lilly Library
Tiller, Terence, 1916-1987
LMC 2528
1 Box 1 standard
The Tiller mss. consists of BBC radio scripts, ca. 1963-1970, written by Terence Tiller.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Acquisition Information
Purchase: 2006
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Biographical Note
Terence Tiller, 1916-1987, was a BBC radio producer and writer. His interests included history, literature, and mythology, and he produced the first BBC radio adaptation of The Lord of the Rings.
Scope and Content Note
The Tiller mss. consists of BBC Radio scripts, ca. 1963-1970, written by Terence Tiller.
Radio; Radio scripts.; Tiller, Terence, 1916-1987; BBC Radio
- Tiller, Terence.Bernard Spencer 1909-63, Selected Poems. Introduced by Terence Tiller. Reader: Denis Goacher., (20 pgs.)
  Scope and Contents
  Mimeographed typescript, corrected, signed, and inscribed by Tiller "as a personal tribute to an old friend."
- Verlaine in England B.B.C., 1963; (39 pgs.)
  Mimeographed typescript signed.
- Bernard Spencer, 1909-1963: Selected Poems, introduced by Terence Tiller B.B.C., (19 pgs.)
  Mimeographed typescript signed and inscribed.
- Poets of the 16th Century: Lyrics from the Minor Elizabethan Stage Lyrics, selected and introduced by Terence Tiller B.B.C., 1968; (14 pgs.)
  Mimeographed typescript signed and with notes on pace, tone and stress of reading in the text.
- Aphrodite the Luxuriant Pig: A Study in Mythology and Folklore, 1970
  - Heavily worked autograph manuscript., (36 pgs.)
  - Corrected carbon typescript., (45 pgs.)
- Design for a Weathercock: A Cool Examination of John Dryden, 1970
  - Autograph manuscript., (34 pgs.)
  - Corrected carbon typescript., (36 pgs.)